https://italianimports.com.au/privacy-policy-product-images/

Skip to main content
Home
Privacy policy & Product Images
Privacy policy & Product Images
At Italian Imports we respect the privacy rights of our visitors and customers and as such place high importance on information collected. We are committed to the protection of any personal information we collect and will only use it lawfully and in your best interests.
Where you have provided your consent we will use your details solely for the purpose of fulfilling your orders and to manage your account. Credit card details are never shared with third parties and are only used in the processing of your order. Additionally, we may also obtain information for the purpose and as a result of authentication or identity checks.
We may at times send you emails and or offers from which you can unsubscribe. Under no circumstances will we sell any of your details to any other party for marketing or other purposes.
All information provided to us is kept strictly confidential and is encrypted before it is sent to us to protect it from unauthorized use.
If you are under 18, we require that you inform a parent or guardian of our Privacy Policy and Term and Conditions as well as requiring their consent before registering or placing an order.
Please ensure that you read the Privacy Policy before submitting your details.
Although we take every care possible to ensure that product images accurately represent posted articles the nature of photography and lighting conditions means that at times colours, textures or shades may differ from the actual article.
Close
×
OK
